Guide to the Time Inc. Life Editorial Records 1937-2013 MS 3009-RG 9
New-York Historical Society
- Series IV.A. Senior Editor Gene Farmer Files, 1958-1972, 2005-2006; 10 Linear feet in 10 record cartons
  - Subseries IV.A.2. First on the Moon: A Voyage with Neil Armstrong, Michael Collins and Edwin E. Aldrin, Jr. Files, 1963-1971, 2005; 230644; 9 Linear feet in 9 record cartons
    - Subsubseries IV.A.2.b. Book Drafts, 1969-1970; 230654; 2 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
      - Original Typescript: Chapter 1-6, 1969; 230663 (Offsite-box 2166, Folder 18-22)
        Includes corrections from Buzz Aldrin and Neil Armstrong.
      - Original Typescript: Chaper 7 to End, 1969; 230664 (Offsite-box 2167, Folder 1-4)
      - Original Typescript: Master Copy Corrected, 1969; 230665 (Offsite-box 2167, Folder 5-8)
      - Original Typescript: Master with Corrections, 1969; 230666 (Offsite-box 2167, Folder 6-8)
      - Original Typescript: Copies, 1969; 230667 (Offsite-box 2167, Folder 9-11)
        Includes corrections from Mike Collins and Schefter (may mean space writer James Schefter).
      - Typescript with Corrections, 1969; 230668 (Offsite-box 2167, Folder 12-13)
      - Typescript with Corrections, 1969; 230669 (Offsite-box 2168, Folder 1-2)
    - Subsubseries IV.A.2.c. Research, 1963-1971; 230670; 7 Linear feet in 7 record cartons
      Research includes background material on astronauts and various space missions such as NASA biography sheets, Time Science news reports, press kits, informational booklets, and press releases from the Apollo News Center; audio cassettes and reels of interviews with the Apollo 11 astronauts and their wives, astronauts from prior missions, and NASA staff; interview transcripts; and news clippings. As separate files were not created for the astronauts wives' transcripts, audiovisual material that only includes them is listed under their husbands. Unreformatted audiovisual material in the collection is not accessible.
      - Astronauts: Miscellaneous, 1969; 230672 (Offsite-box 2168, Folder 3-4)
      - Astronauts: Aldrin, Edwin E. (Buzz), Jr.: General: Papers, 1969; 230673 (Offsite-box 2168, Folder 5-8)
        Includes interview transcripts from him and Joan Aldrin.
      - Astronauts: Aldrin, Edwin E. (Buzz), Jr.: General: Audiovisual [RESTRICTED], 1969; 233087 (Offsite-box 2226)
        Some audiovisual for Aldrin is listed under "Life and Time Inc. Staff."
        1 audiocassette (Sony C-60): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On container: "Joan Aldrin - March 11, 1969."
        1 audiocassette (Sony C-90): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on Side B: "Pat Collins." On container: "Joan Aldrin #2 - Side A - Pat Collins Side B - Part of side A."
        1 audiocassette (Sony C-60): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on container: "Buzz Aldrin - a bad tape."
        1 audiocassette (Scotch C-90): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on one side: "Buzz Aldrin side 3 - Aug 6." Label on other side: "Buzz Aldrin Side 4 - Aug 7 1969." Label on container: "Buzz Aldrin - Aug. 1969."
        1 audiocassette (Scotch C-90): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on Side A: "Buzz Aldrin 8/6/69." Label on Side B: "Buzz Aldrin." Label on container: "Buzz Aldrin."
        1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 5 in., 1/4 in. tape. Label on container: "Aldrin - side 1 - pre-flight."
        1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 5 in., 1/4 in. tape. Label on container: "Aldrin #2 - side 1 - pre-flight."
        1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 5 in., 1/4 in. tape. Label on container: "Aldrin tape 3 - both [sides]."
        1 audiocassette (Norelco C-90): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on Side A: "Ralph Morse - I Transcribed 5/12/69." Label on Side B: "Aldrin I Transcribed 4/11/69."
      - Astronauts: Aldrin, Edwin E. (Buzz), Jr.: General: Audiovisual [RESTRICTED], 1969; 233111 (Offsite-box 2227)
        1 audiocassette (Norelco C-90): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on Side A: "Aldrin 2 [crossed out]." Label on Side B: "Aldrin 2 [crossed out]."
      - Astronauts: Aldrin, Edwin E. (Buzz), Jr.: Gemini 12 Flight, 1966; 230674 (Offsite-box 2168, Folder 9)
      - Astronauts: Armstrong, Neil: Papers, 1963-1969; 230675 (Offsite-box 2168, Folder 10-12)
        Includes transcripts from him and Janet Armstrong, and material regarding Gemini 8.
      - Astronauts: Armstrong, Neil: Audiovisual [RESTRICTED], 233082 (Offsite-box 2226)
        Some audiovisual from Neil Armstrong is listed under Michael Collins.
        1 audiocassette (Sony C-90): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on Side A: "Jan Armstrong - baby Karen and [fire?]." On container: "Jan Armstrong - Side A and part of side B" and "#0644."
        1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 5 in., 1/4 in. tape. Labels on container: "Armstrong #1" and "#0644."
        1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 5 in., 1/4 in. tape. Labels on container: "Armstrong #2 - Side 2 - Side 1" and "#0644."
        1 audiocassette (Scotch C-90): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label: "Side No. 3 - Neil Armstrong - LRL - 8/7/69 and 8/8." On container: "#0644 - Neil Armstrong."
      - Astronauts: Armstrong, Neil: Audiovisual [RESTRICTED], 233099 (Offsite-box 2227)
        1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 5 in., 1/4 in. tape. Label on container: "Jan Armstrong side 1 only. Transcribed 4/2/69 March 1969." On sticky note: "Copied for Hauser."
        1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 5 in., 1/4 in. tape. Label on container: "Jan Armstrong - side 1. Neil Armstrong - Side 1 & 2."
        1 audiocassette (Scotch C-90): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on Side IA: "Armstrong Transcribed 5/5/69." Label on Side IB: "Armstrong Transcribed 5/7/69."
        1 audiocassette (Scotch C-90): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on Side IIA: "Armstrongs Tape 2 Trans. 5/9/1969."
      - Astronauts: Bean, Alan, 1968-1969; 230676 (Offsite-box 2168, Folder 13)
        Audiovisual for Bean is listed under Charles Conrad.
      - Astronauts: Borman, Frank: Papers, 1969; 230678 (Offsite-box 2168, Folder 14)
      - Astronauts: Borman, Frank: Audiovisual [RESTRICTED], 1969; 233085 (Offsite-box 2226)
        1 audiocassette (Sony C-90): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label: "Frank Borman on the cosmonauts." On container: "Frank Borman on cosmonauts."
        1 audiocassette (Scotch C-90): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on Side 1: "Frank Borman trip to Russia Aug-4 1969." Label on Side 2: "Borman Side 2." Label on container: "Borma."
      - Astronauts: Borman, Frank: Audiovisual [RESTRICTED], 1969; 233100 (Offsite-box 2227)
        1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. Label on container: "Frank Borman - Tape 1 & Tape 2 - both on side 1."
        1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 5 in., 1/4 in. tape. Label on container: "Frank Borman Tape 2 (end)."
      - Astronauts: Collins, Michael: Papers, 1969; 230679 (Offsite-box 2168, Folder 15-16)
        Includes interview transcripts from him.
      - Astronauts: Collins, Michael: Audiovisual [RESTRICTED], 1969; 233088 (Offsite-box 2226)
        Some audiovisual from Pat Collins is listed under Edwin Aldrin.
        1 audiocassette (Sony C-90): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on Side A: "Pat Collins." On container: "Pat Collins - Side A and half of Side B."
        1 audiocassette (Scotch C-90): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on [Side 1?]: "Mike Collins LRL Aug. 2, 1969 4:45 p.m. - plus Neil Amrstrong 8/7/69 Side 1." Label on [Side 2?]: "Neil Armstrong Side 2."
        1 audiocassette (Norelco C-60): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on Side A: "Mike Collins - Take 2 8/2/69." Label on Side B: "Collins - Take 2."
        1 audiocassette (Sony C-90): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on container: "Mike Collins - tape 3."
        1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 5 in., 1/4 in. tape. Label on container: "Mike Collins - pre-flight - probably March, 1969."
        1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 5 in., 1/4 in. tape. Label on container: "Mike Collins - #1 - 2 sides."
      - Astronauts: Collins, Michael: Audiovisual [RESTRICTED], 1969; 233101 (Offsite-box 2227)
        1 audiocassette (Sony C-90): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on container: "Side A: Mike Collins #1. Side B: Mike Collins #2."
        1 audiocassette (Sony C-90): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on container: "Side A: Collins #3."
      - Astronauts: Conrad, Charles (Pete): Papers, 1968-1969; 230680 (Offsite-box 2168, Folder 17)
      - Astronauts: Conrad, Charles (Pete): Audiovisual [RESTRICTED], 1969; 233083 (Offsite-box 2226)
        1 audiocassette (Sony C-90): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label: "Pete" with other words crossed out. On container: "Pete Conrad, Tape 1 - Nov. 30, 1969 - Apollo 12."
        1 audiocassette (Sony C-90): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label: "Pete Conrad - Tape 2." On container: "Easter '69 - Pete Conrad, Tape 2 - End - side bow - Apollo 10."
        1 audiocassette (Sony C-90): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On container: "Easter '69 - Pete Conrad - Side A begins ____ needs to be ______."
        1 audiocassette (Sony C-90): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on Side A: "__2 Pete A2 transcribed." Label on Side B: "Al Bean - back is front." On container: "Pete Conrad and Alan Bean - Apollo 12."
      - Astronauts: Gordon, Richard F.: Papers, 1968; 230681 (Offsite-box 2168, Folder 18)
      - Astronauts: Gordon, Richard F.: Audiovisual [RESTRICTED], 1968?; 233084 (Offsite-box 2226)
        1 audiocassette (Sony C-90): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on Side A: "Dick Gordon 1." Label on Side B: "Dick Gordon 2." On container: "Dick Gordon - Apollo 12."
      - Astronauts: Official Biographies, 1967-1968; 230682 (Offsite-box 2168, Folder 19)
      - Astronauts: Transcripts of Interviews, 1963; 230705 (Offsite-box 2169, Folder 1)
        Includes transcripts from Frank Borman, Charles "Pete" Conrad, James McDivitt, Elliott See, and Ed White.
      - Command and Service Modules, 1969; 230708 (Offsite-box 2169, Folder 2)
      - Life and Time Inc. Staff [RESTRICTED], 1969; 233097 (Offsite-box 2226)
        1 audiocassette (Scotch C-90): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label: "Graves Pollard - Farmer meeting on contracts etc. Ap. 26 1969." Label on container: "Graves and Farmer talking to astronauts April 26 1969." and "#0644."
      - Life and Time Inc. Staff [RESTRICTED], 1969; 233110 (Offsite-box 2227)
        1 audiocassette (Norelco C-90): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on Side A: "Morse II Transcribed 5/12/69."
      - The Moon: Technical Data, 1968-1969; 230711 (Offsite-box 2169, Folder 3)
      - Moon Rock: Post-Apollo 11 Analysis, 1969-1970; 230712 (Offsite-box 2169, Folder 4-5)
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA): General, 1969; 230713 (Offsite-box 2169, Folder 6)
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA): Dinner, 1971; 233113 (Offsite-box 2227)
        1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. Label on container front: "NASA dinner-10/7/71. Sulgrave Club. 'Report On America'." Label on container back: "Times, Inc. Oct 7-1971. 3 3/4 IPS." Label on container side: "Tape #6. NASA Dinner. 'Report on America'." Label on reel: "NASA dinner-10/7/71. Sulgrave Club. 'Report On America'."
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Missions: Apollo Program: General, 1968-1969; 230715 (Offsite-box 2169, Folder 7)
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Missions: Apollo Program: Medical, 1968-1969; 230716 (Offsite-box 2169, Folder 8)
        Includes a transcript from the Apollo News Center of an Apollo 8 medical briefing with Dr. Charles Berry.
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Missions: Apollo 7: Papers, 1967; 230717 (Offsite-box 2169, Folder 9)
        Includes transcripts from self-recorded accountings by Wally Schirra, Donn Eisele, and Walter Cunningham.
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Missions: Apollo 7: Audiovisual [RESTRICTED], 1967?; 233102 (Offsite-box 2227)
        1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. Label on container: "Cunningham Tape 1." Label on inside [loose]: "TAPE 1, SIDE 1."
        1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. Label on container: "Cunningham Tape 2." Label on inside [loose]: "NO. 2 THIS SIDE UP." Label on reel: "TAPE 2, SIDE 1."
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Missions: Apollo 8: General, 1968-1969; 230718 (Offsite-box 2169, Folder 10)
        Includes interview transcripts for William Anders, Frank Borman, and Jim Lovell.
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Missions: Apollo 8: Audiovisual [RESTRICTED], 233103 (Offsite-box 2227)
        1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 5 in., 1/4 in. tape. Label on container: "Jim Lovell Tape 1."
        1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 5 in., 1/4 in. tape. Label on container: "Jim Lovell TAPE 2."
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Missions: Apollo 8: Mission Commentary Transcript, 1968; 230719 (Offsite-box 2169, Folder 11)
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Missions: Apollo 8: New York Times / Look Publication, 1969 (Offsite-box 2220, Folder 4)
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Missions: Apollo 9: General, 1969; 230720 (Offsite-box 2169, Folder 12-13)
        Includes interview transcripts from James McDivitt, Dave Scott, Russell "Rusty" Schweickart, a transcript from a self-recorded accounting by Dave Scott, and drafts of articles by Hamblin.
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Missions: Apollo 9: Audiovisual [RESTRICTED], 1969; 233090 (Offsite-box 2226)
        1 audiocassette (Sony C-60): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On container: "Rusty Schweickart Tape I - Apollo 9."
        1 audiocassette (Sony C-60): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On container: "Rusty Schweickart - Tape II - Apollo 9."
        1 audiocassette (Sony C-60): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On container: "Apollo 9 - Tape I."
        1 audiocassette (Sony C-60): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label: "Apollo 9." On container: "Apollo 9 - Tape II - all 3 guys."
        1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 5 in., 1/4 in. tape. Label on container: "Dave Scott - Apollo 9 - side 1 only."
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Missions: Apollo 9: Mission Commentary Transcript, 1969; 230721 (Offsite-box 2169, Folder 14-15)
        Includes transcripts from an Apollo News Center news conference.
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Missions: Apollo 9: Press Kit, undated; 230740 (Offsite-box 2170, Folder 1)
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Missions: Apollo 10: General, 1969; 230741 (Offsite-box 2170, Folder 2)
        Includes transcripts of self-recorded accountings by Eugene Cernan and Thomas Stafford, and a copy of the NASA Recover Requirements.
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Missions: Apollo 10: Audiovisual [RESTRICTED], 1969; 233091 (Offsite-box 2226)
        1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. Label: "Side 2." Label on container: "Gene Cernau - Apollo 10."
        1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. Label on container: "Tom Stafford - Apollo 10."
        1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. Label on container: "Young - John Young - Apollo 10."
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Missions: Apollo 10: Briefings and Press Conference, 1969; 230742 (Offsite-box 2170, Folder 3)
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Missions: Apollo 10: Press Kit, 1968; 230743 (Offsite-box 2170, Folder 4)
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Missions: Apollo 11: General, 1969; 230744 (Offsite-box 2170, Folder 5-7)
        Includes a brochure on spacesuit specifications and a copy of launch instructions.
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Missions: Apollo 11: Early Apollo Scientific Experiments Package, 1969; 230746 (Offsite-box 2170, Folder 8)
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Missions: Apollo 11: Lunar Excursion Module, 1969; 230749 (Offsite-box 2170, Folder 9)
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Missions: Apollo 11: Lunar Landing, Extravehicular Activity and Liftoff from Moon, 1969; 230747 (Offsite-box 2170, Folder 10)
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Missions: Apollo 11: Lunar Receiving Laboratory Status Reports: Post Flight, 1969; 230748 (Offsite-box 2170, Folder 11)
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Missions: Apollo 11: Mission Commentary Transcripts, 1969; 230750 (Offsite-box 2170, Folder 12-15)
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Missions: Apollo 11: Mission Commentary Transcripts, 1969; 230751 (Offsite-box 2171, Folder 1)
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Missions: Apollo 11: Newspaper Clippings, 1969; 230752 (Offsite-box 2171, Folder 2-5)
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Missions: Apollo 11: Press Kit, 1969; 230753 (Offsite-box 2171, Folder 6)
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Missions: Apollo 11: Recovery and Splashdown: USS Hornet: Tommy West Wires, 1969; 230754 (Offsite-box 2171, Folder 7)
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Missions: Apollo 11: Time Science Wires, 1969; 230755 (Offsite-box 2171, Folder 8-9)
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Missions: Apollo 12: General, 1969; 230756 (Offsite-box 2171, Folder 10-11)
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Missions: Gemini Missions, 1969; 230757 (Offsite-box 2171, Folder 12-13)
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Missions: Saturn V, 1968-1969; 230758 (Offsite-box 2171, Folder 14-16)
        Includes photographs of the Mississippi Test Facility.
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Missions: Saturn V, 1969; 230759 (Offsite-box 2172, Folder 1-3)
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Staff: "The Fifteen" (People behind the scenes): Papers, 1969; 230760 (Offsite-box 2172, Folder 4-7)
        Includes interview transcripts or the recounting of interviews with Arnold Brokow, Herman Clark, Walter Delle, Charlie Duke, Robert and Jean Gilruth, Ted Guillory, Lew Hartzell, John Houbolt, Kenny Kleinknecht, Dee O'Hara, Claude Ryan, Wally Schirra, Jack Schmitt, Joe Schmitt, Deke Slayton, Howard Tindall, and Guenter Wendt.
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Staff: "The Fifteen" (People behind the scenes): Audiovisual [RESTRICTED], 1969; 233096 (Offsite-box 2226)
        1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 5 in., 1/4 in. tape. Label on container: "Arnold Brokaw - Geologist - used [in] moon book."
        1 audiocassette (Scotch C-90): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on both sides: "Ted Guillory." Label on container: "Ted Guillory - flight planner for - moon book."
        1 audiocassette (Scotch C-90): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on Side 1: "Jerome Hammack landing and recovery section." Label on container: "Jerome Hammack NASA recovery section - for moon book."
        1 audiocassette (Scotch C-90): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on Side A: "Louisiana Side A." Label on Side B: "Louisiana Side B." Label on container: "Louisiana story."
        1 audiocassette (Sony C-60): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on Side A: "Dee O'Hara." Label on Side B: "Dee O'Hara." Label on container: "Dee O'Hara tape 1 for moon book."
        1 audiocassette (Sony C-90): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on one side: "Dee O'Hara." Label on other side: "Stete" with Dee O'Hara crossed out. Label on container: "Dee O'Hara - Tape 3."
        1 audiocassette (Sony C-90): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label: "Dee O'Hara 3." Label on container: "Dee O'Hara - Tape 3."
        1 audiocassette (Scotch C-90): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on one side: "Wally Side 1." Label on other side: "Side 2."Label on container: "Wally Schirra."
        1 audiocassette (Scotch C-90): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on one side: "Wally Side 3." Label on other side: "Wally Side 4."Label on container: "Wally Schorra [Schirra?]."
        1 audiocassette (Sony C-90): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on Side A: "Deke Slayton." Label on Side B: "Deke Slayton." Label on container: "Deke Slayton - for moon book."
        1 audiocassette (Sony C-90): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on Side A: "Howard Tindall." Label on container: "Howard Tindall - for moon book."
        1 audiocassette (Scotch C-90): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on Side 1: "Guenter Wendt Tape 1, Side I." Label on Side 2: "Guenter Wendt Tape I, Side 2" with Mike Collins Side __ crossed out. Label on container: "Guenter Wendt for moon book."
        1 audiocassette (Scotch C-90): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on Side 1: "Guenter Wendt Tape 2, Side 1." Label on Side 2: "Guenter Wendt Side Tape 2." Label on container: "Guenter Wendt Cape Kennedy - for moon book."
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Staff: "The Fifteen" (People behind the scenes): Audiovisual [RESTRICTED], 1969; 233104 (Offsite-box 2227)
        1 audiocassette (Sentry): analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on Side 1: Walter Delle. Apollo 11 begins [marks a cue on tape]." Label on Side 2: "Delle."
        1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. Label on container front: "Schirra Tape I." Label on container back: "Wally Schirra Apollo 7. Tape #1 @ 3 3/4 inches/sec. SIDE ONE ONLY. almost a full reel. Where there's Hope (Bob). There's LIFE (Dody)."
        1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. Label on container front: "Schirra - Tape 2." Label on container back: "Wally Schirra Apollo 7. Tape #2 @ 3 3/4 inches/sec. SIDE TWO ONLY. About 1/4 of this reel."
      - Notecards, 1970; 230761 (Offsite-box 2172, Folder 8)
      - Press Conferences and Briefings, 1969; 230762 (Offsite-box 2172, Folder 9-10)
      - Soviet Moon Landing, 1968-1969; 230764 (Offsite-box 2172, Folder 11)
        Includes correspondence with physicist and radio astronomer Sir Bernard Lovell.
      - Soyuz 6, 7 and 8, 1969; 230765 (Offsite-box 2172, Folder 12)
      - Space Program: The Future, 1969; 230766 (Offsite-box 2172, Folder 13)
      - Space Shuttle [RESTRICTED], 1969?; 233114 (Offsite-box 2227)